# **CASEY MOTHS**



moths.casey@gmail.com

I am a full stack developer, a creative problem solver, critical thinker and passionate learner. I love new challenges and exploring new technologies and am constantly curious about design and user experience. I have a breadth of skills and look forward to bringing my passion for web development and my eagerness to learn to your organization.

#### **EXPERIENCE**



#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Freelance, San Diego, CA March 2018 - Current

- Design and develop modern responsive websites for small businesses to increase exposure and sales
- Communicate with business owners to identify their requirements, design sites, and outline schedules
- Develop concepts, control project flow, and ensure deliverable milestones are met

#### APPAREL LICENSING COORDINATOR

Mad Engine, San Diego, CA

March 2016 - Current

- Submit, track, and log all pre-production apparel samples and required reports in Licensor systems and through email as needed

### **SKILLS**



### **COURSEWORK**



HTML MongoDB CSS & SASS **Express JSON** Grid & Flexbox Bootstrap Babel Javascript/ES6+ Gulp & Webpack React API's Redux Adobe Photoshop Node Adobe Illustrator

- The Complete Web Developer Course 2.0
- Javascript: Understanding the Weird Parts- Modern Javascript from the Beginning
- Modern React with Redux
- React 16 with Redux
- MERN Stack Front to Back
- The Complete Wordpress Website Business Course
- Object Oriented PHP & MVC

## **EDUCATION**



Professional Certificate in Translation & Interpretation (Spanish/English) University of California - San Diego 2007 - 2009

Bachelor of Arts - Spanish, Legal Studies University of Wisconsin - Madison 2004 - 2007

## **VIEW MY WORK**

